matesmingle.com 2015-03-31

# Mates Mingle

_We gather and utilize various types of information listed below. By using this Site, or by continuing your membership with matesmingle.com, you signify your acceptance of this Policy._

## Types of Information We Collect:

**Public Information** \- You may visit the Web Site anonymously. During your visit, we may collect information that is not personally identifiable such as your IP address, site usage and purchase behavior, browser type, browser activity, and browser settings. 

**Private Information** \- We may collect information about you to provide you with the services that you request. The information we collect may include but is not limited to name, email address, mailing address, phone number, credit card

**Email Information** \- When you become a member of and opt-in to the site, you will automatically be registered to receive promotional offers and updates via email from our mailing partner, All Inbox, LLC.

Customers credit card data will never be sold, shared, or transferred to a 3rd party.

## How do we Protect your Security:

We work to protect the security of your information during transmission by using Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) software, which encrypts information you input. 

We use encryption to protect your information contained in our customer list.

We use a firewall to protect against unlawful intrusion.

We limit access to your information on a "need to know" basis.

## How the Collected Information is Used:

**Public Information** \- We may use anonymous information that we collect about your visit to enhance the operation of the website. For example, we use anonymous information to make the website more navigable or to remember what is contained in your shopping cart or history. We may contract with third-party service providers to assist us to better understand our site visitors and to help us tailor the website function accordingly. 

**Private Information** \- We use the personal data you submit to provide you with the services you request. For example, we may require you to submit personal information to fulfill your order, complete registration on the website, or send you information about our products. We may use this information to personalize your site experience. We may share your personal information as may be required by law or court order or with a law-enforcement or other government agency in connection with a criminal investigation, fraud prevention or other legal action if we reasonably believe it is necessary to do so to protect us, our customers or the public. 

**Email Information** \- When you become a member of and opt-in to the site, you will automatically be registered to recieve promotional offers and updates via email from our mailing partner, All Inbox, LLC.

## Opt-Out and CAN-SPAM Act:

When you become a Member, you will automatically be registered to receive promotional offers and updates, via e-mails, from us and from the Network Sites and other associated e-mail brands. 

Additionally, when you become a Member, you will be provided with the opportunity to receive promotional offers, via e-mails, from partners of ours. While some of these opportunities will only be sent to you if you expressly request them, others may be sent to you unless you elect not to receive them. Accordingly, please review these offers carefully. 

Members may, at any time, choose not to receive promotional e-mails from the site, the Network Sites or partners of ours by following the "unsubscribe" instructions in the applicable e-mail. Notwithstanding the foregoing, we may continue to contact Members for the purpose of communicating information about their membership with us to Members, or similar information relating to us, the Site or your membership, as well as to facilitate, complete or confirm any transaction that Members' enter into or in response to or fulfillment of Members' inquiries or requests. 

Note that unsubscribing from one e-mail list does not automatically unsubscribe you from any other e-mail list that you may be on. Please read the e-mail carefully to find out which list you are unsubscribing from. 

Unless otherwise noted, the Site, e-mails and the content available in connection therewith, are neither intended for, nor directed to, children under the age of 18. Except as otherwise noted, if we learn that a person who is a Member is under the age of 18, we will promptly terminate that individual's membership. 

To operate the Site, including processing your transactions and supporting your activities on the Site, we may share your personal information with our agents, representatives, contractors and service providers so they can provide us with support services such as authorization of credit card transactions, email origination, receipt or support services, customer relationship management services, order fulfillment and sweepstakes and promotional fulfillment. 

To enhance your experience as a Site member, we send out message notifications, newsletters and site announcements, and from time to time third party offers from companies that we feel may have something that will benefit you. Our site provides you with the opportunity to opt-out of receiving different types of communications (except system communications, or communications required for account maintenance), and each email that we send out has a method for opting-out located at the bottom of the message. 

## Changes to our Privacy Policy 

We may, from time to time, amend this Policy, in whole or part, in its sole discretion. Any changes to this Policy will be effective immediately upon the posting of the revised policy. 

If you have any questions or concerns regarding our privacy policy, please contact our support department at [support@matesmingle.com](mailto:support@matesmingle.com).
